{
  "numOfQs": 10,
  "title": "Music Quiz",
  "quizitems": [{
    "questiontext":"\"They got married early, never had no money\" is the first line of which classic Australian song?",
    "answertext":"'To Her Door' by Paul Kelly and the Coloured Girls",
    "choices":["'To Her Door' by Paul Kelly and the Coloured Girls",    
     "'Beds are Burning' by Midnight Oil",
     "'Listen Like Thieves' by INXS",
     "'Khe Sahn' by Cold Chisel"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"Complete this lyric from the song by The Animals. \"There is a house in New Orleans, they call the….\"",
    "answertext":"Rising sun",
    "choices":["Red house",    
     "Rising sun",
     "House on the moon",
     "Cool house"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"Aretha Franklin’s 1967 hit song ‘Respect’ was written, and originally performed, by",
    "answertext":"Otis Redding",
    "choices":["Simon and Garfunkel",    
     "Diana Ross",
     "Marvin Gaye",
     "Otis Redding"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"The 2010 album by Scottish band Belle and Sebastian is called",
    "answertext":"Write About Love",
    "choices":["Tigermilk",    
     "Dear Catastrophe Waitress",
     "Write About Love",
     "If You’re Feeling Sinister"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"Complete this lyric from Michael Jackson’s ‘Thriller’. \"It’s close to midnight, and something evil’s lurking in the….\"",
    "answertext":"Dark",
    "choices":["Wind",    
     "Air",
     "Dark",
     "Trees"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"In the Flaming Lips song \"She don't use jelly\", what does the girl use to make her hair \"real orange\"",
    "answertext":"Tangerines",
    "choices":["Tangerines",    
     "Saffron",
     "Something you buy at the store",
     "Food colouring"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"From which You am I song is the following line? \"I’m like a waterlogged ball, that no one wants to kick around anymore\"",
    "answertext":"Heavy Heart",
    "choices":["Purple Sneakers",    
     "Berlin Chair",
     "Heavy Heart",
     "Mr Milk"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"The 1980’s hit song \"Take on Me\" was performed by",
    "answertext":"A-ha",
    "choices":["Wham!",    
     "A-ha",
     "Duran Duran",
     "Flock of Seagulls"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"Prior to becoming an opera singer, Luciano Pavarotti worked as a",
    "answertext":"School teacher",
    "choices":["School teacher",    
     "Plumber",
     "Chef",
     "Gardener"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"“\"Wide Open Road\" is a classic Australian song originally performed by which band?",
    "answertext":"The Triffids",
    "choices":["The Church",    
     "Hunters and Collectors",
     "Icehouse",
     "The Triffids"]
  }]   
}